may checking in
Bastien you and make the perfect
research assistants will we
me I love reading your journal I'm so
jealous you get to go to all those
places that's true I guess you don't get
to travel very much
get cold just looking at you they you
should look somewhere else
you're just a no-good bully how can you
even look at yourself in the mirror I
beg your pardon I consider myself a
freedom fighter a misunderstood one I
hate bullies like you that's cold
you are terrible that's cold
hame agree do you know what time it is
well I'd say it's about now I see what
you're doing there
dr. Ziegler I don't think you've aged a
day since I last saw you
and neither have you May
may you haven't aged a day what's your
secret
cryostasis but I'm not sure if I'd
recommend it
look at all the snow we should make snow
angels why are you looking at me May
the frontlines and no place for a
scientist I guess it's a good thing have
you to watch my back
I was wondering if I could take a look
at your little robot
I suppose so just keep the hammer to
yourself
chase' you're so amazing you inspire me
Mei you're the real hero
are you born wearing all that yes but is
too late to change
I love your glasses so cute oh um thanks
I like yours too
we should compare notes sometime that
would be great what's your opinion on
the Tobel Steen's gravitational models
seiyya I don't understand how you can
fight in the code wearing so little I'll
tell you my secret if you give me a coat
Zaria how can you even pick up all that
weight I lift as well as I lift because
this can won't be avoided
Winston is so awesome just like so